KEVIN WU

ENTREPRENEUR / DESIGNER / DEVELOPER

EDUCATION

2013 - Present

University of California, Berkeley

Electrical Engineering / Computer Science

PROJECTS

2015

The Resistance

The Resistance is a popular board game that has sold nearly half a million copies. I led and recruited a team of developers in partnership with the licensed publisher to build an official mobile adaptation for iOS and Android.

ø unboard.io/resistance

2015

Epic Everything

Led a team of over 30 people in building and marketing a Unity real-time collectible card game. Raised over \$40,000 on Kickstarter before pivoting and ultimately deciding to open source the project.

epic-everything.com

2014

Elevate Africa

Elevate Africa is a nonprofit that supports entrepreneurs in the poorest regions of Africa. They needed a website and crowdfunding system. I led a team of designers and developers in building it in Ruby on Rails.

ø elevateafrica.herokuapp.com

2013

USOMC

USOMC has been an internationally recognized music competition for youth since 1992. I helped design and develop a website for them in Ruby on Rails with an extensive competition management system.

 ø usomc.herokuapp.com

EXPERIENCE

2015 - Present

Hobo Labs

Game Designer / UI/UX Designer
Worked on a mobile dungeon crawler game.
Designed core game mechanics like the
enemy types and the skill system. Also
designed the general UI/UX flow.

2014 - Present

Unboard

Founder / CEO

Unboard is a game studio that brings the magic of tabletop games to the mobile world. We were in the startup accelerator Free Ventures for Fall 2014, and have so far earned over \$10,000 in revenue.

2013 - Present

Blueprint

Developer / Project Leader / VP of Projects
Blueprint directly partners with nonprofits
and develops a web or mobile application for
them pro bono. I developed and led multiple
projects for nonprofits.

calblueprint.org

2015

Leada

Web Developer / UI/UX Designer
Leada is a Y Combinator-backed online data science course provider. I redesigned and redeveloped their website to reflect a change in their target market, from consumers to businesses and universities.

2014

Salesforce

Mobile Developer / UI/UX Designer
Designed and developed several enterprise
mobile applications in Apex and Visualforce
on the Salesforce1 platform.

PROFILE

■ kevintxwu@gmail.com

408 813 7875

kevinandstuff.com

github.com/kevintxwu

AWARDS

2015

Thiel Fellowship Finalist

Thiel Fellowship

Was one of 70 finalists interviewed out of nearly 3000 candidates for a prestigious two year \$100,000 grant program.

2014

Design For Good Hackathon First Place

Blueprint / Innovative Design
Built the Calciumulator for the American
Bone Health nonprofit organization.

o calciumulator.herokuapp.com

2014

CMYK Designathon First Place

Innovative Design

Designed a water conservation campaign called Save The Bae.

SKILLS

Design

Illustrator / Photoshop / Wireframing Flowcharting / Graphic Design

Web

HTML / CSS / SCSS / Javascript / jQuery AngularJS / PHP / Ruby on Rails

Programming

Unity / Python / Java / C / C++ / C#
Objective-C / Ruby / Scheme / Lisp / MIPS
Git / GitHub / Unix